Willowbrook Review Panel; Records apap127
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED], 1975-1980; 3; 19.3 cubic ft.
  - Staffing Audits [RESTRICTED], 1978-1980; 3.3; 1.5 cubic ft.
    - Staffing Audit, Data [RESTRICTED], 1978-1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
    - Staffing Audit, Data, Bernard Fineson Developmental Center [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
    - Staffing Audit, Data, Bernard Fineson Developmental Center [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
    - Staffing Audit, Data, Bronx [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
    - Staffing Audit, Data, Kings Park [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
    - Staffing Audit, Data, Manhattan Developmental Center [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
    - Staffing Audit, Data, Willowbrook Health Services Unit, Buildings 10, 11, 25 [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
    - Staffing Audit, Data, Willowbrook Health Services Unit, Buildings 27, 32, Basic Research Institute [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
    - Staffing Audit, Data, Willowbrook Health Services Unit, Buildings 6, 7, 8 [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
    - Staffing Audit, Data, Willowbrook Health Services Unit, Buildings 9, 19, 32 [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)
    - Staffing Audit, Data, Willowbrook Unit II, Buildings 5, 21 [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 29)
    - Staffing Audit, Data, Willowbrook Unit II, Buildings 33, 76, 77 [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 30)
  - Program Audits [RESTRICTED], 1977; 3.4; 0.2 cubic ft.
    This series consists of files on audits conducted at psychiatric centers where former Willowbrook residents were receiving care. The purpose of the audit was to determine whether the residents' needs for educational and recreational programs were being met according to the terms of the Consent Decree.
    - Program Audit, Psychiatric Center [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
    - Program Audit, Psychiatric Center [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
    - Program Audit, Psychiatric Center [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
  - Operational Audits [RESTRICTED], 1977-1979; 3.5; 0.9 cubic ft.
    The Review Panel also conducted operational audits of New York State's mental retardation services. This subseries consists of data, draft reports, recommendations, and responses to operational audits.
    - Operational Audit [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
    - Operational Audit, County Services Group, Audit Instrument [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
    - Operational Audit, County Services Group, Data [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
    - Operational Audit, Data Sheets [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
    - Operational Audit, Data Sheets [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
    - Operational Audit, Data Sheets [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
    - Operational Audit, Documentation [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
    - Operational Audit, Facilities Development Corporation [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
    - Operational Audit, Facilities Development Corporation [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
    - Operational Audit, Pre-Audit Materials and Notes [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
    - Operational Audit Recommendations [RESTRICTED], 1976-1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
    - Operational Audit Report, Draft [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
    - Operational Audit, Report, Draft [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
    - Operational Audit, Report, Draft [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
    - Operational Audit, Report, Draft [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
    - Operational Audit, Response, Borough Developmental Services Office [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
    - Operational Audit Response, Draft [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
  - Surveys [RESTRICTED], 1975-1977; 1979-1980; 3.6; 1.5 cubic ft.
    The bulk of this series consists of self-surveys completed by Willowbrook related facilities as part of the audit process. Also included are summary reports of an Intermediate Care Facility (ICF) survey completed in each of the five boroughs of New York.
    - IFC Survey, Brooklyn, Summary [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
    - IFC Survey, Bronx, Summary [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
    - IFC Survey, Manhattan, Summary [RESTRICTED], 1979-1980 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
    - IFC Survey, Queens, Summary [RESTRICTED], 1979-1980 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
    - IFC Survey, Staten Island, Summary [RESTRICTED], 1979-1980 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
    - Self Survey, Bernard Fineson Developmental Center [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
    - Self Survey, Bernard Fineson Developmental Center [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
    - Self Survey, Bernard Fineson Developmental Center [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
    - Self Survey, Bernard Fineson Developmental Center [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
    - Self Survey, Brooklyn Developmental Center [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
    - Self Survey, Brooklyn Developmental Center [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
    - Self Survey, Brooklyn Developmental Center [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
    - Self Survey, Brooklyn Developmental Center [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
    - Self Survey, Brooklyn Developmental Center [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
    - Self Survey, Forms [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
    - Self Survey, Kings Park [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
    - Self Survey, Kings Park [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
    - Self Survey, Kings Park [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
    - Self Survey, Kings Park, Correction [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
    - Self Survey, Manhattan [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
    - Self Survey, Manhattan Developmental Center, Gouveneur Service Center [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
    - Self Survey, Manhattan Developmental Center, Keener Unit [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
    - Self Survey, Manhattan Developmental Center, Keener Unit [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
    - Self Survey, Manhattan Developmental Center, Sheridan Unit [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
    - Self Survey, Manhattan Developmental Center, Sheridan Unit [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
    - Self Survey, Manhattan Developmental Center, Sheridan Unit [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
    - Self Survey, Suffolk Developmental Center [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
    - Self Survey, Suffolk Developmental Center [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)
    - Self Survey, Wassaic [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 29)
    - Self Survey, Wassaic Developmental Center, Wingdate Unit [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 30)
    - Self Survey, Wassaic Developmental Center, Wingdate Unit [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 31)
    - Self Survey, Wassaic Developmental Center, Wingdate Unit [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
    - Self Survey, Wassaic Developmental Center, Wingdate Unit [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
    - Self Survey, Wassaic Developmental Center, Wingdate Unit [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
    - Self Survey, Wassaic Developmental Center [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
    - Self Survey, Westchester [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977 (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
    - Self Survey, Westchester [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
    - Self Survey, Westchester [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
    - Self Survey, Westchester Developmental Center [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
    - Self Survey, Westchester Developmental Center [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
    - Self Survey, Westchester Developmental Center [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
    - Self Survey, Westchester, Developmental Center [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
    - Self Survey, Westchester Developmental Center, Questionnaire [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 2 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
  - Audit Administrative Files [RESTRICTED], 1977-1980; 3.7; 0.9 cubic ft.
    This subseries contains files on the general administration of the audit process. The bulk of the series concerns the development of the standardized audit instrument used to measure compliance at Willowbrook and other state facilities. Also included are instructions for auditors, memoranda, files on audit recommendations, and correspondence with the New York Department of Mental Health's Technical Assistance Unit regarding audits conducted jointly with the Review Panel.
    - Audit Findings Comparison [RESTRICTED], 1978-1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
    - Audit Instructions and Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1977-1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
    - Audit Instrument Development [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
    - Audit Instrument, Draft, Comments [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
    - Audit Instrument, Materials for Revision [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
    - Audit Instrument, Materials for Revision [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
    - Audit Instrument, Materials for Revision [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
    - Audit Instrument, Pilot [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
    - Audit Instrument Revision [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
    - Audit Recommendations [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
    - Audit Recommendations [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
    - Audit Recommendations #2 Re: Clients Rights [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
    - Audit Recommendations #4 Re: Psychiatric Services and Medication [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
    - Audit Recommendations: #6, Community Placement/Respite Care [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
    - Audit Recommendations: #7, Food and Nutrition [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
    - Audit Recommendations, Community Placement and Related Facilities Audits [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
    - Audit Recommendations Compliance Status [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
    - Audit Standard Revision [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
    - Audit Team [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
    - Audit Team 4 [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
    - Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
    - Cross- Reference Worksheets [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
    - CSG Audit Instrument [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
    - Expansion of Audit Process, Memoranda [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
    - Joint Audit Compliance Analysis, Memoranda [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
    - Sample Client Activity Schedule Record [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
    - Technical Assistance Unit, Joint Audit Instrument, Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
    - Technical Assistance Unit Joint Procedures, Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 1 (3-Audits and Surveys [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)
- Compliance [RESTRICTED], 1975-1980; 4; 16.0 cubic ft.
  This series contains materials on consent Decree compliance generated by state developmental centers. Many folders in Subseries 1 and four within Subseries 2 are restricted because they contain lists of Willowbrook clients and/or information about clients' medical conditions. These restricted folders are noted below in the box and folder list.
  Arranged alphabetically, then chronologically.
  - Willowbrook Compliance [RESTRICTED], 1975-1980; 4.1; 11.6 cubic ft.
    This subseries is comprised mostly of 90 day progress reports produced by Willowbrook authorities for the Review Panel. The reports contain unit demographic descriptions, compliance inventories, compliance plans, progress narratives, and assurance statements. Also included in this subseries are files from the initial Willowbrook compliance survey of 1975, operational plans for Willowbrook Developmental center, and files related to the Staten Island Audit Compliance Task Force. At the end of the subseries are several folders containing reports on the status of Willowbrook non-residential clients.
    - 90 Day Progress Report [RESTRICTED], 1977 July-1977 September (Box 1 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Assurance Statements [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 1 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Auxiliary Departments [RESTRICTED], 1976 April-1976 June (Box 1 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Building Self-Surveys [RESTRICTED], 1977 April-1977 June (Box 1 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Buildings 14-16 and 26 [RESTRICTED], 1978 October-1978 December (Box 1 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Bronx Unit, April-June [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 1 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6-11)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Brooklyn Unit [RESTRICTED], 1976 April-1976 June (Box 1 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12-18)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Central Program Services [RESTRICTED], 1977 July-1977 September (Box 1 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Central Program Services [RESTRICTED], 1977 October-1977 December (Box 1 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Clinical Deputy Director [RESTRICTED], 1977 January-1977 March (Box 1 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports,Clinical Deputy Director [RESTRICTED], 1977 October-1977 December (Box 2 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Clinical Deputy Director [RESTRICTED], 1978 April-1978 June (Box 2 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Clinical Deputy Director [RESTRICTED], 1978 July-1978 September (Box 2 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Clinical Deputy Director [RESTRICTED], 1978 September-1978 December (Box 2 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4-5)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Clinical Deputy Director [RESTRICTED], 1979 April-1979 June (Box 2 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Complete Unit Reports [RESTRICTED], 1976 January-1976 March (Box 2 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7-9)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 2 [RESTRICTED], 1975 September (Box 2 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 2 [RESTRICTED], 1975 October-1975 December (Box 2 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 2 (Behavior Modification Unit) [RESTRICTED], 1975 September (Box 2 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 2 (Convalescent Care Unit) [RESTRICTED], 1975 September (Box 2 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 5 [RESTRICTED], 1975 September (Box 2 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 5 [RESTRICTED], 1975 October-1975 December (Box 2 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 6 [RESTRICTED], 1975 September (Box 2 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 6 [RESTRICTED], 1975 October-1975 December (Box 2 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 7 [RESTRICTED], 1975 October-1975 December (Box 2 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Buildings 7 & 9 [RESTRICTED], 1975 September (Box 2 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 8 [RESTRICTED], 1975 September (Box 2 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20-21)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 8 [RESTRICTED], 1975 October-1975 December (Box 2 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 10 [RESTRICTED], 1975 September (Box 2 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 10 [RESTRICTED], 1975 October-1975 December (Box 2 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 11 [RESTRICTED], 1975 September (Box 2 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 11 [RESTRICTED], 1975 October-1975 December (Box 3 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 12 [RESTRICTED], 1975 September (Box 3 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 12 [RESTRICTED], 1975 October-1975 December (Box 3 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 13 [RESTRICTED], 1975 September (Box 3 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 13 [RESTRICTED], 1975 October-1975 December (Box 3 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 14 [RESTRICTED], 1975 September (Box 3 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 14 [RESTRICTED], 1975 October-1975 December (Box 3 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 15 [RESTRICTED], 1975 September (Box 3 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 15 [RESTRICTED], 1975 October-1975 December (Box 3 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 16 [RESTRICTED], 1975 September (Box 3 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 16 [RESTRICTED], 1975 October-1975 December (Box 3 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 19 [RESTRICTED], 1975 September (Box 3 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 19 [RESTRICTED], 1975 October-1975 December (Box 3 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 20 [RESTRICTED], 1975 September (Box 3 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 20 [RESTRICTED], 1975 October-1975 December (Box 3 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 21 [RESTRICTED], 1975 September (Box 3 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 21 [RESTRICTED], 1975 October-1975 December (Box 3 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 22 [RESTRICTED], 1975 September (Box 3 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 22 [RESTRICTED], 1975 October-1975 December (Box 3 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 23 [RESTRICTED], 1975 September (Box 3 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 23 [RESTRICTED], 1975 October-1975 December (Box 3 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 25 [RESTRICTED], 1975 September (Box 3 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 25 [RESTRICTED], 1975 October-1975 December (Box 3 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 26 [RESTRICTED], 1975 September (Box 3 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 26 [RESTRICTED], 1975 October-1975 December (Box 3 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
    - 90 Day Progress Reports, Compliance Status Surveys- Building 27 [RESTRICTED], 1975 September (Box 3 (4-Compliance [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)